Hmm?
Hey, I've never seen you before.
Are you from here?
Are you alone?
Come here, with us.
You must be hungry.
Here.
My name's Pil.
The Scratcher and Fluffy.
If you want, you can
be part of our gang.
But first of all, what
are we going to call you?
Wait, I know.
Gobbly.
Come on, I'll explain how
things work around here.
This is our city,
called Foggyborough.
The motto of the city
is, to build the kingdom,
one must find where
nobility resides.
You get it?
Yeah, me neither.
The old king came up with it...
Theobald.
See that guy there?
That's Tristain.
He's the one who governs right
now, but he's not the king.
He's just the regent.
That's the guy who's going
to be our next king...
Roland.
Prince Roland.
To be honest, Gobbly,
we don't really
care who governs around here.
We're orphans.
We live on the street,
and the nobles sure
aren't going to take care of us.
So we've got to
fend for ourselves.
OK, hold on tight, Gobbly.
Woo-hoooooo!
Woo-hoo!
Yeah!
You OK, Gobbly?
When we want something
to eat, we go see Crobar.
This time, that pesky
sprite won't escape me.
And Crobar thinks I'm
some kind of sprite.
He thinks I've got magic powers.
Now watch this.
That sprite won't be able
to resist this mince tart.
Oh, cockerel.
You see that?
I'm not dreaming.
I know it's that pesky sprite.
Now, where's he hiding?
A-ha!
There you are, cockerel.
I didn't see that one.
Now, just you wait.
Pesky little sprite.
I'll catch you, cockerel.
Make way.
Make way for Lord Tristain.
What on earth are
you doing, Crobar?
It's that sprite, Lord Tristain.
I'm trying to catch that
pesky little sprite.
A sprite?
Yes, Lord Tristain, a sprite
that loves to eat mince tarts.
And if I manage
to catch him, then
maybe I can become a knight,
and that would be a great...
Achievement?
Crobar, the only
thing you're achieving
is proving you're
a good-for-nothing.
Crobar, a knight.
What a laugh.
Poor Crobar.
He's not even close
to becoming a knight.
Anyway, thanks to him we
have mince tarts every day.
Come on, pass me the ball.
Come on.
Here, catch.
Hey.
Hey, over here.
Throw it.
Go on.
Pass it.
OK, throw it to me.
Here.
No, you kicked it too hard.
I kicked it too hard?
I can do what I want.
Come inside right now, children.
That's the sprite.
Don't go near him.
But...
Yay!
Prince Roland, I've
ruled over this kingdom
since your father died,
and I've done very well.
Since I've been regent, I've
had the commoners at my feet.
They give me all their
wealth, without complaint,
because they fear me.
I levy more and more taxes,
and they don't oppose me.
And you... you think that
because it's your birthday
I'll just hand you the throne.
Never.
Do you know what I'm going to
give you for your birthday?
This!
Ha!
Ha ha!
Happy birthday.
Here, take that.
Who's the smart one now?
Uh, Lord Tristain?
I was passing by
and heard noise.
You OK?
Yes, yes.
I just had a little
craving for chicken.
Huh?
OK.
Well, good night, Lord Tristain.
Good night, Prince Roland.
It'll be your last.
Hear... Hear ye, hear ye.
Oh, come on.
Enough with the tooting already.
Good.
Hear ye, hear ye, you
citizens of Foggyborough.
Today is the 20th birthday
of our dear Prince Roland.
He's henceforth of age
to take the throne.
Rejoice, and bring food
for the great coronation
banquet for all the
nobles of the realm.
Come forward.
Come no, come on.
Provisions for the
banquet go over there.
Cold meats go in the back,
and vegetables on the side.
Ah, cheese.
Put that in the shade, please.
Hello, good sir.
And what did you bring?
Lovely mince tarts
for the banquet.
Mmm.
Can I see?
No, no, they're for the Prince.
All right, over there.
Go on.
Eat as much as you want.
But keep it down, OK?
Gentlemen, damsels, make way for
the minstrels and troubadours,
who will feel this
castle with music and fun
on this wondrous occasion.
Joy and gaiety
will feel the air.
Forget about your worries,
and enjoy a happy troupe.
Wow.
Come on, Jiggler.
Hurry up.
Yes, yes, I'm coming.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
I'm coming, coming.
Whaaaa...
Jiggler.
Look, Jiggler, you've got
to put a bit of effort, OK?
It's the Prince's
coronation, so we need
you to give it all you've got.
And try to be funny for once.
Ah, in that case, I think this
is a job for Mr. Destardo.
Hello.
No, no, no, not that puppet.
Oh, come on.
Please, Lugan, just
one or two jokes.
I'm sure they're going
to love Mr. Destardo.
No, they will not
love Mr. Destardo.
Every time you take
out that puppet,
you make fun of the nobles.
No, no, this time it has
nothing to do with them.
It's just a little riddle.
What's the difference between
a rainbow and a noble at work?
You might at least see
a rainbow sometimes.
He's funny, huh?
Jiggler, if you
disrespect Lord Tristain,
he'll lock us up
under the tower.
Understand?
Yes, Lugan.
Come on, let's go.
And put away that puppet.
You heard him, Mr. Destardo.
I'm so sorry, but you
can't go on tonight.
Lugan, you're censoring me.
I'm not afraid to tell
the truth to the nobles.
You... you just bow to them.
You're a coward, Lugan.
A coward and a jerk.
Jerk, Lugan.
You're a jerk. J...
J... J... jingle bells, jingle
bells, jingle all the way.
Jingle bells, jingle..
No more puppets.
Hello.
Do you know how happy
I am to hear you laugh?
You're the first person
to think I'm funny.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold your horses
there, freckles.
You're not the one
she finds funny.
I am.
You fool, you.
I love what you do with
that little sock puppet.
Excuse me?
What did you call me?
You're the old sock.
This is Mr. Destardo.
My name's Jiggler.
My name's Pil.
Make way.
Make way for Duchess Alienor.
Aunt Alienor, hello.
Oh, Roland, my puddins.
Who is this Duchess Alienor?
She's Prince Roland's aunt.
Oh, you're going to be king.
My brother Theobald
would be so proud of you.
What a great day
for the kingdom.
Come closer, dear.
Come.
There's something you must know.
A short time before
he died, your father
hid a treasure, a treasure
he bequeathed to you.
A treasure?
He said, in order to find it,
you absolutely have to go...
Did you hear that, Jiggler?
There's a treasure
hidden in Foggyborough.
Oh, it would be great
if I could find it.
Nobility resides.
Do you understand?
No.
Yeah, me neither.
But do think about it.
And whatever you do,
don't tell Tristain.
If he knew, he might...
Ah, Prince Roland
and Duchess Alienor.
Oh, Tristain, guess
you're unemployed now.
Yes, yes.
What's with all the trunks?
Are you moving?
Oh, I just brought a selection
of clothes for the ceremony.
I want to look presentable
for my nephew's coronation.
Anyways, I'll leave you be.
I'll go pick out my outfit.
See you.
Your aunt is charming as ever.
Prince, if you
would come with me.
I'd like to speak with
you before the coronation.
I hope that sprite doesn't
come and bother us today.
Say, aren't those the mince
tarts the old man brought?
I better check to see if they're
not too salty because sometimes
they put too much salt.
Mince tarts that bite
and move by themselves?
Cockerel!
Alert!
There's an intruder
in the courtyard!
An intruder!
Pesky sprite.
We have to go up to the dungeon?
Yes, what I have to say
is very confidential.
Are dungeons usually
this high up?
No, Gobbly, that's poison.
Hey, isn't that Lord
Tristain, with a sorceress?
Huh?
Oh, no.
Gobbly, don't touch anything.
You want us to get
caught or what?
Huh?
What are these weird potions?
I think you did something here.
Going up stairs and
having armor is tiring.
Yes, well, whose idea was it
to walk around in armor all day
long?
OK, Tristain, what do
you want to talk about?
The throne.
I've been governing
for 15 years,
waiting for you to come of
age and succeed your father.
That day has come.
If you don't feel ready, if
you'd rather take more time,
if you'd rather wait
another year or two,
I would understand.
I'd understand completely.
No, Gobbly.
So what do you think?
Would you like that?
I stay a bit longer
on the throne?
Oh, no, no, don't
worry about that.
It's time for me to face
my responsibilities.
I'll manage.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
I know it doesn't
always seem like it,
but I'm not as big
an idiot as I look.
That's enough.
Quite enough.
If you really want
to take the throne,
there's only one thing to do.
We'll have a little
toast to celebrate, OK?
A small toast.
Shh, doggy, don't make a sound.
I'll give you a taste of
one of my special drinks,
and you can tell
me what you think.
A toast to my coron...
Your coronation.
To Foggyborough.
Yes, there we go.
Ah, my dear Roland, I've
got a story to tell you.
I think it'll interest you.
It's the story of a young
boy, a young boy who
looked up to his king.
Long live the King.
Long live King Theobald.
He dreamt of being
cheered by the crowd, just
like him, to wear the
crowd, to sit on the throne.
But his destiny was to learn
magic, like his godmother.
The young boy didn't
want this as his destiny,
so he altered it.
He developed a potent poison
to get rid of the King.
But there had to be a culprit,
so he accused his godmother.
It was her.
She fled and took refuge in the
scariest place in the kingdom,
the Cursed Forest.
Today, the only thing
standing between the boy
and being crowned
king is the Prince.
Hey, hey.
Oh dear Roland, did it
go down the wrong way?
Trouble digesting
the poison perhaps?
Oh, what a pity.
The Prince struck down
by a mysterious illness
on the day of his coronation.
And I will remain in power.
Wh... Nugget?
Where are you, Nugget?
Oh, well, I'd better
get going now.
You're not going anywhere.
I'm afraid you're in the
wrong place at the wrong time.
Sorry, but I can't
leave any witnesses.
Is he not dead yet?
Did I mix up the ingredients?
It doesn't matter.
First, the urgent
and then the Prince.
Pesky sprite, I know I
saw you come up here.
I got to get in shape.
What?
Prince Roland?
Prince?
Oh, cockerel.
You OK, Prince?
Oh, the sprite.
Crobar?
Yes, it's the sprite, and
he's bewitched the Prince.
Catch him, Crobar.
Catch him.
Come back here.
Come here, you
pesky little sprite.
I'll teach you to turn
our prince into a chicken.
More stairs.
No, wait, come back, Prince.
It was a joke.
That didn't go as well
as I'd hoped it would.
Ow, ow, ow.
Got a stitch in my side.
Excuse me.
Working.
Coming through.
Like a stampede of Clydesdales.
Looks like you've got a
big problem, Prince Roland.
And I think I'm the only
person who can help you.
Luckily, I'm willing
to help you out.
But in exchange I want the
treasure your father left.
It's up to you.
Good luck.
Tore through here and
sent everything flying.
It's quite insane.
What is it?
Oh, get away, you beastly thing.
So thought about my proposition?
Tristain, thank goodness.
The guard just
tore through here,
sending my outfits flying.
You do realize what a
scandal this could cause?
You have to do
something, Tristain.
That guard, the one who
manhandled my outfit.
It's a deal.
And then there was this beast
that was very ugly, hideous.
A beast you say?
Where did it go?
It went that way.
When Theobald was king...
Yes, yes.
This would never
have happened.
Tell me, milady, have
you seen a sprite go by?
A sprite?
No.
And a chi-cat?
A what?
Yeah, you know.
It's half cat, half chicken.
So a chi-cat.
Oh.
Yes.
And I probably
shouldn't tell you this,
but the chi-cat
is Prince Roland.
Oh, no, poor Prince Roland.
And your furry friends,
have they seen the chi-cat?
No, no, no.
My friends haven't
seen it, Crobar.
Wait, how do you know my name?
Well, it's... it's... it's
because everyone knows Crobar.
Everyone knows that you're the
bravest guard in Foggyborough.
No!
Yes.
Among the nobles, everyone
says that you'll soon
become a knight.
Oh, the Prince!
My treasure.
Let the banquet begin.
How am I going to find
him in all of this?
I'll help you, Crobar.
Really?
You would do that?
Of course.
I am a princess.
It's my job to help princes.
Cockerel, is that true?
You're a princess?
Yes, yes, I sure am a princess.
OK, look.
You go that way, and
I'll go this way.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
please give a round of applause
for the irresistible,
the hilarious Jiggler.
Please try to be funny.
Hey.
Hello.
Do you want to laugh?
I've got what you need.
I have one joke with
two punch lines.
Punches get it?
Whoa, this is one tough crowd.
More funny.
More.
So what is square and yellow?
The sun.
Yeah, I lied.
The sun isn't square.
Remind me again why I keep
this kid in the troupe.
Because he's your nephew, Lugan.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
Anyway, at least he's
not using the puppet.
Who would like to
pull my finger?
You, madam?
Give me that.
Hey, hey, hey hey.
Let go of that, madam.
That's not him either.
What is brown, soft,
and smells like poo?
It's poo.
Any luck, Crobar?
I haven't found him.
He can't be far.
Keep looking.
How about this one?
What do you call a knight
who's sure of himself?
Sir-tainly.
Get it?
Certainly?
Sir-tainly.
So bad.
Jiggler.
Oh, hey there, Pil.
Can you help me?
Can you take out Mr. Destardo
to liven up the atmosphere?
OK, friends, it's time
for me to introduce
my partner, Mr. Destardo.
Oh, no, please not the puppet.
Hello!
Play some music loud, very loud.
Did you hear about the
nobel who paid his taxes?
No?
Yeah, me neither.
Don't like that?
No?
OK, moving on.
How about a riddle then?
Faster.
How do you recognize a thief
who steals from the kingdom?
He wears a crown on his head.
Louder.
Faster, louder.
Let me through.
Out of my way.
What's the difference between
a cushion and Lord Tristain?
At least the cushion
belongs on the throne.
Prince Roland.
The chi-cat.
My treasure.
Move aside.
I need to get by.
Here kitty chi-cat.
Move aside.
Don't be scared.
Come here, little prince.
Did you like that?
They're very good, Nugget.
A little too good.
We're going to need some
help to eliminate the Prince.
It's quiet, huh?
What did you say?
She said, it's quiet.
Ha!
We sure spoiled the
nobles' dinner, didn't we?
Come on, Prince.
Let me take you
back to the castle,
and we'll go see Tristain.
He'll know how to help you.
Hey, what's gotten into him?
I'll take care of him, Crobar.
I'm a princess.
I'm supposed to take
care of princes.
You can go back to
chasing your sprite now.
OK, goodbye.
Oh, well.
All right.
You see?
I kept my word.
I got you out of the castle.
Now we have to make
you human again.
We'll go see that sorceress
in the Cursed Forest.
She must really hate Tristain.
She'll help you.
After that, I'll
get my treasure.
Princess, where are you going?
You're not going to
leave without us?
Yes.
But after everything
that's happened,
Mr. Destardo and I are, well,
unemployed and looking for work
right now.
Could you maybe hire us?
No.
Are you sure, Princess?
If you don't hire
us, Princess, I
might have to have a word or
two with our friend Crobar
about that pesky little
Foggyborough sprite
he's looking for.
Oh, come on, Jiggler.
You wouldn't turn
me in, would you?
I wouldn't, but he would.
Would you stop it.
He's your puppet.
Oh, no, he's my human.
It's not the same.
Fine.
You can come with me.
Where are we going?
To find the sorceress
in the Cursed Forest.
Woo-hoo!
We're going to
the Cursed Forest.
Where is that anyway?
Well, I don't really know.
It's due west, about
a day's journey.
But you really
shouldn't go there.
Why not?
Because the Cursed Forest is
a forest that's been cursed.
Yeah, we figured
something like that.
You know the way?
Yes, I used to gather mushrooms
there when I was young.
Back then, it
wasn't that cursed.
But now it's much more cursed.
Come on, Crobar.
Are you really
afraid of a forest?
Not just any forest, Princess.
A cursed one.
You want to become a
knight, right, Crobar?
Yes.
What if I helped you with that?
Seriously?
For sure.
I'm a princess.
It's my job.
I can make anyone a knight.
I just need to do that
thing with the sword
on the shoulders.
What's it called again?
It's called dubbing.
Oh, right, that's it.
Take us to the Cursed
Forest, Crobar.
Help us turn the Prince
back into a human.
And, boom, I'll
dub you a knight.
That would be an
honor, Princess.
That's great.
Put it there.
Onward to the Cursed Forest.
My humor is at your
service, Princess.
And my weapon will
protect you, Princess.
Cockerel.
Just think, that's
actually Prince Roland.
Yeah, well, that's what you
get when nobles intermarry.
Now, Jiggler, a little respect.
Please remember the
princess is a noble as well.
It wasn't me.
It's him.
Make way.
Make way for Princess Pil.
Step aside, good people.
Make way.
Crobar, do you have to do that?
Yes, Princess.
I have to make sure that you are
given the respect you are due.
The respect that I'm due?
Princess.
Your respect, Your Highness.
Greetings, Princess.
Hello.
Yoo-hoo.
Wow.
Wow, the Princess is beautiful.
Your Highness.
It's not that bad
being a princess.
Looks like somebody's
getting a big head.
Jiggler, your sock needs
to show some respect.
Hey, did she call
me a sock again?
Enough, Mr. Destardo.
Now bow to the princess.
No, I don't bow down to anybody.
That's enough.
Back in the pocket.
No, not the pocket.
Please not the pocket.
It's dark in here.
Let me out!
Dash those worries.
Sing out loud.
The cat is a chicken.
The chicken a cat.
Together we're strong,
and nothing will stop us.
Cockerel, beware.
Your Highness.
Princess.
Prince...
Huh?
Dash those worries.
Sing out loud.
The cat is a chicken.
The chicken a cat.
Together we're strong,
and nothing can stop us.
Cockerel, beware.
Sing it.
Sing a melody.
The catch is a chicken.
The chicken a cat.
Raise your head, and
keep moving forward.
Nothing can stop us now.
Prince Roland!
Crobar, I'm hungry.
Yes, Princess, I'll
be right there.
Oh, it's too hot, Crobar.
Oh, yes, sorry.
Now it's too cold.
A thousand pardons, Princess.
I'll get you another bowl.
Fetch them for my
weasels as well, Crobar.
Yes, yes.
There you are.
Enjoy your meal, Princess.
Poor dear, sleeping outside
when you're a princess.
So sad.
You have promised to make
me a knight, Princess.
That has been my dream.
I wanted to thank you somehow,
so I made this modest gift
for you.
Hey, watch it, Princess.
You're becoming as
snobby as a real noble.
Crobar?
That's very pretty.
Thank you.
Glad to be of service, Princess.
Pardon?
I don't understand
what you're saying.
What are you doing here?
Ahh.
I need to make some
people disappear,
and I'll pay you for it.
Ah, yes.
Eliminating people
for a little money.
We can do that for
sure, but it's a shame.
Really?
Why's that?
Because right now we've
got a subscription plan!
Subscription plan?
Yes, we offer quality
service, professionalism.
We adapt to each client.
Satisfaction guaranteed.
For example, with our
special ambassador plus,
you can have unlimited
assassinations
on whoever you please,
with a bonus of torture.
We
We plunder.
We burn.
And we hurt little kitty cats.
Oh, no, we stopped doing that.
Sorry.
All right, then.
I guess I'll take
the ambassador plus.
Yeah!
Ambassador plus,
ambassador plus.
Congratulations.
However, the ambassador
plus subscription,
as you can imagine,
costs a little extra.
Money is not a problem.
Now, the four individuals
that must disappear.
Four?
I'm afraid four is too many
for the ambassador plus.
You're going to need to sign
up for the premium plan.
Yeah, premium plan.
Premium plan.
Oh, all right.
I'll take the pre...
Are you trying to play
me for a fool here?
Yes, I guess I am.
Well, at least I tried.
So who are the four individuals
you want to disappear?
These guards... will you
let me finish my sentence?
What I was going to
say was, these guards
will show you the
way they're headed.
But now they won't be
able to do anything.
Come on, follow me.
I'm really tired of this lot.
Be careful because from
here on in it's cursed.
And over there is
really, really cursed.
This isn't too bad, but
it's cursed just the same.
So be careful.
Yoo-hoo.
Sorceress, yoo-hoo.
Where are you?
For 15 years, she's been
living here all alone?
Maybe she's gone a little...
A little what?
A little nutso.
And this coming from a
guy who talks to a sock.
Look, we'll have a better chance
of finding her if we split up.
Everybody choose a path to take.
Good luck.
OK, splitting up in
the Cursed Forest.
Good idea.
All right, be brave.
You won't let some
Cursed Forest scare us.
No sir.
It's just a forest
that's a bit cursed.
Madam sorceress, yoo-hoo.
Hey, Jiggler.
You want to quit
jiggling so much?
I think I might have
heard something.
Oh, cockerel.
Hmm?
Huh?
Crobar.
Jiggler.
Over here.
Did you find something?
Yes, look over here.
The sorceress left
her footprints.
But they stop right here,
as if she flew away.
Did you hear that?
Yes, that sounds close.
At this very moment, she
could be right behind us.
Let's all turn around
at the same time.
Yeah, all right.
We'll turn on 3.
Ready?
1.
2.
2 and 1/2.
3.
I guess she's not here.
You don't belong in here.
Get out right now.
But we need your help to save
the prince of Foggyborough.
I don't care about
Foggyborough, and I
don't care about the Prince.
Now get out of here.
Wait, what are you
doing, Princess?
Huh?
It's the story of a young boy.
He developed a potent poison
to get rid of the King,
so he accused his godmother.
It was her!
You're a stubborn one.
I know you weren't the
one who poisoned Theobald.
I know that you
are a good person.
You will help us save
the Prince, right?
I've changed.
You don't know what
it's like to be
hunted, to live alone like an
animal to avoid being captured.
Yes, I know exactly
what it's like.
But if you help me
save the Prince,
that will all change for me.
It's fine.
She's going to help us.
Yeah?
We must act fast, or the Prince
will stay like this forever.
To prepare the antidote,
I'll need one very
special ingredient.
And what would that be?
The dung from a unicorn.
Do unicorns really poo?
Yes.
And there's only
one place on Earth
you can find the
dung of a unicorn,
in the Glen of the Beast.
A beast?
Like a werewolf?
No.
This beast is much
worse than a werewolf.
You will take the mountain
path until you reach the Glen.
When you get there,
don't linger.
Pick up the poo, and
get out of there.
Whatever you do, stay
out of the shade.
Hold on.
Is this going to be dangerous?
You came into the Cursed
Forest, looking for a sorceress
to break the spell that turned
the Prince into a chi-cat.
Yes, it's going to be dangerous.
What did you expect?
Well, if it's dangerous, we'd
better leave the Prince here,
right?
Yes, he'll be safe here with me.
Oh, yeah?
See that, Jiggler?
Turns out the sorceress
isn't nutso after all.
Yum, yum.
Yum, yum, yum.
Come on, Nugget.
Find them.
There you go.
At least with this,
you won't catch a cold.
Thanks, Crobar.
That's funny.
With that hood on, she reminds
me of the Foggyborough sprite.
Oh, yeah, you're right, Crobar.
Go on, catch her.
Catch her.
No, no, no, no,
it's a joke, Crobar.
He's joking.
Yeah, I know.
I get it.
This is it.
We're in the Beast's territory.
The Beast!
It's got me!
Run!
Hey, Shee Shee, that's enough.
Stop bothering these people.
Come here.
Oh, don't be afraid.
She's gentle, but sometimes
she gets a little hungry.
Oh, no, not my mince tart.
That was my last one.
Well, Shee Shee sure does
love those mince tarts.
So what brings you
up around here?
We're looking for a unicorn.
You're too funny, you.
There's no such
thing as unicorns.
Hey, look, Crobar.
Over there.
We found it.
Only thing is it's in the shade.
I'll go, Princess.
You sure?
Yes, it's my duty.
Be careful, Crobar.
Unicorn.
I come here every
day with my sheep.
If there was a unicorn around,
I'm sure we'd have seen it.
Right, Shee Shee?
It's clouding over, cockerel.
We don't have seasons
anymore, I'm telling you.
What is it?
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Pil, behind you!
Hey, there we go.
Didn't turn out to be
that hard after all.
Hurry!
Come on, run, Jiggler!
Run for your life!
You can do this.
Yes, yes, that's it.
You're really going fast now.
Are you flying?
Oh, never mind, Jiggler.
Jiggler!
Princess, go find shelter.
I'll take care of the Beast.
I'll get you out
of there, Jiggler.
Thanks, Crobar.
Hey, you're hitting
Jiggler, you big oaf.
Cockerel.
That's all right.
Oh cockerel, I dropped my poo.
I think I did too.
Crobar, you have proven that
you deserve to be a knight.
Keep the unicorn busy
while we grab the bag.
Yeah, but how?
Here, catch.
At your service, Princess.
Come on, Shee Shee.
Catch that mince tart.
Get it.
Yes.
It's OK, Crobar.
We got the bag.
Come on, Crobar.
Hang on tight.
Come back.
I told you there's
nothing to be scared of.
If there's a unicorn here, I
would have seen it for sure.
Oh, darn it.
I split my pants again.
I don't believe it.
We did it.
We're going to save the
Prince and complete our quest.
And I'm going to
become a knight.
Sir Crobar the Knight.
Don't you think you
should tell him the truth?
Sir Crobar the Knight.
Well, you coming?
Yeah, we're coming, Crobar.
Yeah, that's dead.
Flower of hellboar,
slime of a slug,
venom from a viper, and
dung from a unicorn.
Sir Crobar the Knight.
There we are.
The antidote is ready.
Drink this.
Hey.
It worked.
Yeah, but he's buck naked.
He needs undies.
Undies!
Undies, undies,
undies, undies, undies.
Here.
It's all I could find.
Thanks.
There we go.
Looks good, huh?
Mission accomplished.
We saved the Prince.
I swear to honor and serve
you till I die and fight
for the cause of justice.
I am ready to become
your loyal knight.
You can't become
a knight, Crobar.
Because I'm not a real princess.
I stole this dress when you were
chasing me through the castle.
Huh?
Wait, so you're the sprite?
Is that it?
Yeah, I am.
You lied to me.
You manipulated me.
Why would you do all that?
To get to the treasure
that Theobald stashed away.
And I thought you
were so honorable.
In fact, you only want the gold.
That's the only
thing you care about.
It's time the nobles learn
to share their wealth.
I didn't do it for pleasure.
I did it to survive.
You think it's easy, being an
orphan, living on the street.
Doesn't matter.
That's no excuse
for being dishonest.
I really trusted you.
I thought you respected me.
I'm an idiot.
An idiot.
Crobar.
No, wait.
Go talk to him, Pil.
It's never too late to
ask for forgiveness.
Crobar.
Tristain, it's been a long time.
My dear godmother,
I wish you no harm.
I just came to get the Prince.
You're too late, Tristain.
I will not let you hurt him.
I don't think you fully
understand the situation.
We're going to burn everything.
Yes, burn everything.
Aim.
Fire.
And you, Crobar.
I knew you were a
good-for-nothing but not
a traitor.
No, Crobar!
Pil!
Tristain!
No, no.
Leave me alone.
Pil!
Lord Tristain has returned.
Oh, cockerel, I'm leaving.
What's happened?
People of Foggyborough, I have
some very sad news to announce.
The horrible sorceress,
who, as you all remember,
poisoned our good
King Theobald, is back
and kidnapped our prince,
with her foul accomplices.
She dragged Prince Roland
into the Cursed Forest
and then threw
him into an abyss.
Oh, my poor darling.
And now he's dead.
Dead.
Dead, dead, dead.
Duchess.
These criminals
shall be executed.
After that, we'll proceed
with my coronation.
Oh, yes.
Since the Prince can no longer
take his place on the throne,
I gladly volunteer
to be your new king.
It's what Roland
would have wanted.
Crobar.
Jiggler.
Roland?
Pil, I don't want to impose, but
could you please help me again.
Hold on.
We've got to get to
Foggyborough before Tristain
hurts our friends.
You kept your promise, Pil.
You saved my life.
You've earned my
father's treasure.
Look, I don't care about
your father's treasure.
Really?
OK.
Well, that works out
well because truth
is, I don't know where it is.
But I thought your
aunt told you?
Not really.
She just said, in
order to find it,
my father had left
a riddle to solve.
To build... what was it?
"To build a kingdom, one must
find where nobility sits."
Oh, you know it?
It's the town's motto, Roland.
Everyone knows it.
I knew it sounded familiar.
OK, hold on, Roland.
This might get bumpy.
Woo-hoo!
Watch out.
Out of the way.
Excuse us.
Look, the Prince in his undies.
What did you say?
She said, it's the
Prince in his underwear.
Keep going, Pil.
I'll meet you there.
All right, let's get started.
Stop!
That's Pil.
She's alive.
Woo-hoo!
Huh?
I thought she was dead.
Jiggler!
Tristain is a liar.
He's the one who tried
to kill Prince Roland.
What do you mean tried?
I killed... that's
not what I meant.
And he's also the one who
poisoned King Theobald.
That's horrible.
What nonsense.
Seriously, who's going
to believe this urchin?
They'll believe me.
Oh, cockerel, it's Prince
Roland in his undies.
So he's not dead either?
When I kill people and
they don't stay dead,
it gets on my nerves.
Listen, there's been a
terrible misunderstanding.
Let me explain what
really happened.
Oh, look behind you.
It's horrible.
What?
Where?
What is it?
What?
You lied to be king here!
Don't let him get away.
Crobar, I'm really
sorry I lied to you.
It's all right, Princess.
It's all right.
You don't have to call
me Princess anymore.
Whatever you want, Princess.
Hey, what about me?
Group hug.
Catapults, ready.
And fire!
We can't stay here.
We have to leave the city.
And let Tristain win?
No way on Earth.
I'll teach him not to
go after my friends.
And I must prevent him
from using his magic
on Foggyborough.
Mr. Destardo and I will
sabotage the catapults.
Excuse me?
All right, I'll go
get reinforcements.
I'll open the
portcullis, Prince,
so you can get
inside the castle.
Perfect.
Now let's do this.
This is a rotten plan.
Let's go, let's go.
All right, go guard
the portcullis.
George, you got the
ramparts, and try
not to fall off this time.
Tristain.
Godmother.
You must stop this madness.
Why have you become so cruel?
I am not cruel.
I'm powerful, and I
intend to stay that way.
Drink this, Nugget.
Hi there.
Hi.
A fire!
I'm on fire!
Fire!
People of Foggyborough, forward!
Attack!
Take that.
That's it.
Hit them hard.
Throw them back.
Come on, do something.
Move.
Hey, George, that's a mace in
your hand, not a mutton chop.
And you, Alrick, are you afraid
of scratching your shield
or what?
Don't make me come down there.
What was that?
What are you doing?
Me?
Nothing.
I was... well, I'd
better be going.
Wait right there, you.
I've never seen this
guy before in my life.
We're goners.
Run, Jiggler!
Run!
Run for your life!
This is bad, Mr. Destardo.
No, no, we'll be safe in here.
Don't worry.
Maybe not.
Nugget, get rid of her.
Hey, what say we
just talk this over?
Fire, fire, fire!
Water!
I need water!
Jiggler, be honest with me.
Do I have flaming
undies on my head?
Yes, Mr. Destardo.
Get them off of me!
That's bad.
Hey, Jiggler, I can't blow.
Hold the door, Mr. Destardo.
I'll take care of it.
Oh, cockerel, that
was not water.
What do we do now?
We yell.
Oh, good idea.
Pil.
You have to make him drink this.
No!
Pil needs you now.
Oh, no, Pil.
I need powder for the cannon.
Let me in.
Let me get out.
Jiggler, where are you?
I need powder for the cannon.
I can't help you, Crobar.
I'm stuck in here.
Jiggler, if I hold the
door, you can go help him.
Go on.
But, Mr. Destardo, then you'll...
Yes, I won't get out of here.
Mr. Destardo, what am I
going to do without you?
You've got what it takes to
be a great jester, Jiggler.
Me, I'm nothing but a sock.
Maybe, but you're
also my best friend.
You've got other friends now,
and they need you, Jiggler.
I'll always be with
you in your heart.
Now tie me to this
door, and finish this!
See, little girl,
that's what you
get for acting like a princess.
No one can stop me.
Hurry up, Jiggler.
Goodbye, Mr. Destardo.
Things are getting
hot in there, fool.
Oh, mommy.
I got you.
Thanks, Jiggler.
No problem.
I've had enough of this.
Guys, get out of here now!
Prince Roland, raise
the drawbridge.
All right, Crobar.
Come on, we can make it.
We can make it.
We made it!
Let her go, Nugget.
No!
Well done.
Crobar, this potion
will slay that dragon.
I'll take care of it.
Come here, you filthy beast.
Oh, no.
Poor Crobar, did
you actually think
that you could slay a dragon?
You think you're knight worthy?
Come on, open your eyes.
You're a good-for-nothing.
I'm sorry, Princess.
I can't protect you.
He's right.
I'm a good-for-nothing.
My loyal Crobar, you have
served and protected me,
with honor and courage.
Would you do me the
honor of being my knight?
Yes, Princess.
Do you swear you'll fight to
uphold justice and fairness?
I swear I will, Princess.
Then I hereby dub you my knight.
You are Sir Crobar
of Foggyborough.
I always knew you
were noble, Princess.
Noble in your heart.
Of course.
That's the answer to the riddle.
Tristain, hold on.
I have something that
might interest you.
"To build a kingdom, one must
know where nobility resides."
Nobility is in your heart.
What is that?
A treasure?
Yes, the Theobald treasure.
You want it, don't you?
Oh, yes.
Then come and get it.
My treasure.
Gobbly, the chew toy.
Just paper?
What kind of treasure is that?
I'll get you for
this, you little brat.
You don't stand a chance.
Nugget, do you want
a yummy chew toy?
Princess, meeting you is the
greatest adventure of my life.
Crobar!
Prince Roland, you saved me.
Undies!
I need some undies!
Come on, Nugget.
Nugget, quickly.
Get out of here now.
And don't you ever set
foot in Foggyborough
again, you scoundrels.
Yeah, don't come back!
Pil.
Crobar.
Where are you, Pil?
Pil.
Crobar?
Crobar.
Crobar, don't leave me.
I need you here.
Can you hear me?
Wake up, Crobar.
That's an order, you hear me?
You're my loyal knight
now, and you must obey me.
Don't leave me, Crobar.
At your service, Princess.
Crobar.
Thank you.
Thank you, my friends.
Thanks for everything you
did for me and Foggyborough.
Of course.
This is it, the
Theobald treasure.
Hey.
I don't know you.
You're not from here.
Are you all alone?
If you want, you can
join our little gang.
This is Foggyborough.
Would you like to
meet my friends?
Woo-hoo!
Hello, madam sorceress.
So how are the
magic classes going?
Great.
My new pupils are fast learners.
Oh, wow.
Ah, Pil, have you seen how
well the construction's going?
Look at that, my
father's treasure.
Yeah, well, actually
the treasure is mine,
but I decided to share
it with everybody.
The first orphanage
in Foggyborough,
and over there a library
open to every citizen
to enjoy, and there a hospital
to take care of sick people
in town.
That's right.
The treasure was a
plan, instructions
for a new village King Theobald
wanted to build for his people.
Hey, ho.
Time to eat, cockerel.
Crobar.
My little princess.
Come on, mince tarts
for everyone, cockerel.
Hey, hey, I've got a joke.
What's the difference between
King Roland and a brick wall?
Hold on, let's play
some music, huh?
And loud.
A brick wall isn't as thick.
He said, thick as a brick wall.
I don't get it.
Dash those worries.
Sing out loud.
The cat is a chicken.
The chicken a cat.
Together we're strong,
and nothing can stop us.
Cockerel, beware.
Dash those worries.
Sing out loud.
The cat is a chicken.
The chicken a cat.
Together we're strong,
and nothing can stop us.
Cockerel, beware.
Sing it.
Sing a melody.
The cat is a chicken.
The chicken a cat.
Raise your head, and
keep moving forward.
Nothing can stop us now.
Ladies.
I liked him better
in his undies.
Me too.
Oh, the brick wall.
It isn't as thick.
I get it.